Prophet T.B. Joshua's arrives in the Dominican Republic.
In preparation for the crusade in the Dominican Republic.
with Prophet TB Joshua.
This is the International Airport, José Francisco Peña Gómez;
and a lot of Dominicans with dream in their hearts for miracles, have gathered here today to witness
the momentous arrival of Prophet TB Joshua to this nation.
Crowds Await The Arrival Of Prophet T.B Joshua In The Dominican Republic
Dignitaries, National Police And Security Officials Await The Arrival Of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Major Mendoza Rosario
Dominican Republic National Police
It is an honour for me to be here today, to serve the community.
His name is Major Mendoza from the national police here in the Dominican Republic
and its an honour and privilege for him to be here to welcome Prophet T.B Joshua today.
The expectation not only of myself but of the people is great because our people, town, world
needs a person like Prophet T.B. Joshua to come and bring life to them,
to the Dominican people that are so much in need of this.
There are many things happening in our community and we wish that with the coming of
Prophet T.B. Joshua, people will really begin to understand the importance of family values.
He believes that it is not just his expectation but the expectation of all the people in this country to see that
they really need a man like T.B Joshua in this land.
This is a very special happening that will touch every home and families have to be united,
what every home and family should do
keep positive expectations, believe in God, love Him and seek Him the more.
positive expectations, care for
The impacts of this nation and the change will be in that, the people will
honour God more and believe Him more.
Colonel Edgar Hamburgo Rincon
Sub Regional Director, Dominican National Police
His name is Colonel Hamburgo and he is the Sub Director of a section of the Police force.
Here in the Dominican Republic.
Everyone knows that wherever the Prophet goes, many miracles happen.
wherever the prophet goes,
We hope that in our country;
We expect the same thing to happen in our country; our expectation is very positive for his visit.
We know that wherever the Prophet is there are always miracles.
In Jesus' name; and we believe that the same thing will happen in our
nation, in Jesus' name.
We know that God does miracles through the prophet and we hope that our nation will,
like others, be changed - for the authorities, the sick and everything that belongs to our nation.
He said that he believes that he whole nation will be changed through the miracles
that will happen. The authorities will be changed; and the sick people. It will
be a change that will bless their nation. Thank you so much.
Pastor Jose Carlo Puertollano
Spain
I am the Pastor Jose Carlo Puertollano, and I am here from Spain.
We went to The SCOAN four years ago; we saw the glory of God
and we have a lot of expectations because we know where Prophet T.B. Joshua steps,
there is a change; the kingdom of God comes to the nation in healing, deliverance and prophecy.
We are very excited about what God is going to do in this nation which is why we flew so many
Kilometres to share in what God is about to do through Prophet T.B. Joshua.
We know that thousands of people are going to be healed and delivered in the name of Jesus Christ.
We have great expectations. Four years ago we were in SCOAN and we came
here from Spain, because we know wherever prophet T.B Joshua arrives
there is healing, there is deliverance, there is prophecy and there is great
change and great healing for that nation. So that is why we took all
those miles to be able to be here and spend this time and be part of this with
Prophet T.B Joshua.
Awaiting The Arrival Of Prophet T.B. Joshua In Dominican Republic
Prophet T.B. Joshua Arrives In Dominican Republic
The Arrival Of Prophet T.B. Joshua In Dominican Republic.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Arrives At Presidential Palace, Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic
Shortly after his arrival to the nation, Prophet T.B. Joshua was invited by the president
of the Dominican Republic, Danilo Medina, to meet with him
at the presidential palace in the nation's capital city.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Arrives At Presidential Palace, Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic
The man of God is welcomed and let into the palace.
As he enters the grand hall, he is greeted by Bishop Elvis medina, the link between
the government and the christian community in the Dominican Republic.
The bishops of presiding christian councils across the nation extend their warm welcome to the man of God.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Welcomed By Leading Bishops Of The Dominican Republic
Prophet T.B. Joshua At Presidential Palace, Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic
Prophet T.B. Joshua is led into another room where president Medina has been waiting for him.
Here, the prophet meets the 53rd president of the Dominican Republic, Danilo Medina.
All are seated and the historic meeting between the prophet and the president begins.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Meets Dominican Republic President, Danilo Medina
Corrected: Juliet Bwalya 09/06/2018